Merrimack Films records 7064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Merrimack Films records
1972-2018
1940-2019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Merrimack Films
Bass, Suzanne R.
Bass, Henry
Schlaifer, Peter
7064
70 film reels. 35mm film canisters
30 cubic feet.
The Merrimack Films records, 1972-2007, includes film scripts, research files, catalogs, promotional materials, and audiovisual materials documenting the operations and output of Merrimack Films.
16403221
Box 71
Box 72
Box 73
Box 74
Box 1
Box 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6
Box 7
Box 8
Box 9
Box 10
Box 11
Box 12
Box 13
Box 14
Box 15
Box 16
Box 17
Box 18
Box 19
Box 20
Box 21
Box 22
Box 23
Box 24
Box 25
Box 26
Reel 27
Reel 28
Reel 29
Reel 30
Reel 31
Reel 32
Reel 33
Reel 34
Reel 35
Reel 36
Reel 37
Reel 38
Reel 39
Box 40
Reel 41
Reel 42
Reel 43
Reel 44
Reel 45
Reel 46
Reel 47
Reel 48
Reel 49
Reel 50
Reel 51
Reel 52
Reel 53
Reel 54
Reel 55
Reel 56
Reel 57
Reel 58
Reel 59
Reel 60
Reel 61
Reel 62
Reel 63
Reel 64
Reel 65
Reel 66
Reel 67
Reel 68
Reel 69
Reel 70
Biographical / Historical
Merrimack Films was founded in 1983 by Henry Bass to produce and distribute films and videos on labor relations. The company is located in Belmont, Massachusetts. Bass received a BA from Williams College and an MA in economics from Harvard University. Before becoming a film and video maker, he taught labor and marketing at Hunter College. Merrimack Films' productions are as follows:
Loose Bolts? (1973), made in collaboration with Peter Schlaifer Crisi Bargaining (1979) Givebacks (1983) Union Democracy (1986) Union in Crisis (1992) Working Together: Saturn and the UAW (1994) Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers (1996) Trouble Partnerships (1999) Struggling Unions (2002) Rustbelt Phoenix (2006) What Happened to Saturn? (2008)
Scope and Contents
The Merrimack Films records, 1972-2007, includes film scripts, research files, catalogs, promotional materials, and audiovisual materials documenting the operations and output of Merrimack Films. Of particular note are the contents of Series III which contains original film footage on various audiovisual formats used in the production of the company's films. Correspondence and notes from Henry and Sue Bass can also be found throughout the collection.
Bass, Suzanne R.; Bass, Henry
16403221
- Series I. Film Files, 1972-2011
  Scope and Contents
  Contains research files, clippings, correspondence, reviews, promotional materials, and transcripts related to documentaries produced by Merrimack Films.
  - Loose Bolts?, 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Loose Bolts? brochure, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Loose Bolts? royalties, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Blow For Blow brochure, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes brochure and discussion guide, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Crisis Bargaining, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Three Classics: Loose Bolts?, Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Crisis Bargaining brochure, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Crisis Bargaining brochure and discussion guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Givebacks, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Givebacks brochure, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Four Classics: Loose Bolts, Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Crisis Bargaining, Givebacks brochure, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Union Democracy, 1985-1991 (Box 71, Folder 13-16)
  - Union Democracy, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Union Democracy brochure, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Union Democracy, Loose Bolts, Givebacks promotional letter, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Unions in Crisis, 1985-1992 (Box 71, Folder 20-23)
  - Unions in Crisis brochure and promotional letter, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Five Labor Classics: Loose Bolts, Crisis Bargaining, Givebacks, Union Democracy, Unions in Crisis brochure, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Working Together: Saturn brochure update, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994-1995 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Working Together/Loose Bolts promotional letter, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW brochure, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Saturn, 1987-1994 (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Saturn sequel, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 10-11)
  - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers brochure, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Jointness sequel (Partners), 1938, 1991-1996 (Box 73, Folder 5-9)
  - Troubled Partnerships, 1996-1998 (Box 71, Folder 32-34)
  - Troubled Partnerships, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Troubled Partnerships brochure, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Troubled Partnerships (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Partners, Troubled Partnerships, Working Together brochure, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Merrimack Films: Films and Values on Labor Relations brochure, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Struggling Unions, 1996-2001 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
  - Congressional Committee, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and stickers, 1998-2000 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Struggling Unions, 1998-2006 (Box 72, Folder 6-8)
  - Carpenters, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Teamsters, 1998-2001 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Struggling Unions, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Michael Ansara, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - UAW-Pontiac, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - George Cashman, 2000-2001 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Struggling Unions visuals, 2001-2002 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Struggling Unions comments, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Struggling Unions brochure, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Struggling Unions update, 2002-2007 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Rustbelt Phoenix, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 19-20)
  - Rustbelt Phoenix, 2002-2015 (Box 72, Folder 21-23)
  - Rustbelt Phoenix, 2003-2007 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Rustbelt visuals, 2002-2006 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Rustbelt Phoenix 2, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Rustbelt/What Happened to Saturn? reviews and responses, 2006-2009 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Rustbelt auto sequel, 2006-2011 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Rustbelt Phoenix brochure, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - What Happened to Saturn? correspondence, 2002-2007 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - What Happened to Saturn? brochure, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Saturn timeline, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - I.a. Future Films
    Contains clippings and notes saved by Merrimack Films for potential documentary projects originally housed in a file labeled "Future Films."
    - Foreign Auto, Undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - NAFTA, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Jointness sequels, 1991-1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Trainwrecks, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Employee rights, 1981-1994 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Steel, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Union Crisis 2, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - New Zealand, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Saturn sequel, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Non-union worker rights, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Union Democracy update, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Series II. Office Files, 1940-2019; 1975-2019
  Contains correspondence, notes, research, advertisements, and customer order information.
  - About Merrimack Films, Undated (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Harold Rutenberg, 1940-1996 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Brochures, reviews, correspondence, 1975-2000 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Unemployment film (not made), 1980-2008 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Sam Salkin correspondence, 1983-11-02 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Red Ball Films acquisition, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Viewer comments, 1987-1991 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Victor Reuther, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Customer survey, 1993-2003 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - United Air Lines (a film considered but not made), 1996-2003 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Une 2 film, 1997-2004 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Notebook, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - UNITE update, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Bruce Kaufman, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Jo Ann Gardner, 1999-2000 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Tire plant update, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Polaroid/Bridgestone update, 2000-2002 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Nissan/Saturn/Henderson, 2001-2005 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, orders, brochure drafts, 2002-2003 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - SEIU, 2002-2004 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Interest Based Negotiations at Kaiser Permanente seminar, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Notebook, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Henry Bass business cards and Saturn visitor pass, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Une 2 film - jobs, 2007-2010 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - Connect the Docs, 2007-2014 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - Une 2 film - Economist film project, 2011 (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence and orders, 2012-2014 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - Merrimack Films sale advertisement, 2018-2019 (Box 74, Folder 46)
- Series III. Audiovisual Materials, 1973-2007
  - III.a. 16mm Film
    - Union Democracy, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 23, Item 24)
      1 reel on core.
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 1)
      2 reels on cores.
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 2)
      1 reel on core. Old Internegative.
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 3)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 4)
    - Taxes, Taxes; Loose Bolts: Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 5)
      7 small reels on cores, plus three paper strips. Internegatives.
    - Union Democracy, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 25, Item 6)
      2 reels on cores. "B" winds.
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 3)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 4)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 5)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 6)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, 1977; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 7)
      1 small reel on reel.
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 8)
      1 small reel on core. Negative.
    - This Negative No Good, Undated; 16mm Film (Box 26, Item 9)
      3 small reels on cores.
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 27)
      1 reel on reel.
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 28)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 29)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 30)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 31)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 32)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 33)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 34)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 35)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 36)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 37)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 38)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 39)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 40)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 41)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 42)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 43)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 44)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; 16mm Film (Reel 45)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 46)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; 16mm Film (Reel 47)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; 16mm Film (Reel 48)
    - No Title, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 49)
    - Blow For Blow, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 50)
    - Blow For Blow, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 51)
      4 reels on cores.
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 53)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 54)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 55)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 56)
    - Givebacks, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 57)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 58)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 59)
    - Miscellaneous Lordstown, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 60)
      13 small reels on cores.
    - Miscellaneous Lordstown, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 61)
      6 small reels on cores.
    - Miscellaneous Lordstown, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 62)
      11 small reels on cores.
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 63)
      2 reels on reels.
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 64)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 65)
      7 small reels on cores; 1 small reel on reel; 2 small reel not on cores or reels; 1 paper strip.
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 66)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Taxes, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 67)
    - The Unemployed, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 68)
      2 reels on core.
    - No Title, Undated; 16mm Film (Reel 70)
      4 small reels on cores.
  - III.b. Betacam/Betamax
    - Givebacks, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Givebacks Narration 1, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 5)
      Driving in car, Len talking ambience sound from car
    - Givebacks Narration 2, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 6)
      Opening and closing
    - Merrimack Films/National Archives, 1985-05-16; Beta (Box 2, Item 7)
      7 videos
    - Ron Carey 1 Unions in Crisis, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 8)
      Original
    - Ron Carey 2 Unions in Crisis, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 9)
    - Kennedy School Interview Tape 1, 1996-02-14; Beta (Box 2, Item 10)
      tape 020
    - Kennedy School Interview Tape 2, 1996-02-14; Beta (Box 2, Item 11)
      tape 021
    - Merrimack Films A, 1989-12; Beta (Box 2, Item 12)
    - Merrimack Films (NARS) B, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 13)
      5 videos
    - They'll Never Keep Us Down, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 15)
      The story of the United Mine Workers of America struggle with the Pittston Company
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 16)
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 17)
    - National Archives Working Summary, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 18)
    - General Working Summary, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 19)
    - General Summary 2, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 20)
    - Ford Collection Tape 1-3, 1985-10-24; Beta (Box 2, Item 21)
      Dub with burned-in time code
    - Ford Collection Tape 4; Cannon Mills Tape 1-4, 1985-10-24; Beta (Box 2, Item 22)
    - Kansas City #1, 1985-07-10; Beta (Box 2, Item 23)
      Dub
    - Kansas City #2, 1985-07-10; Beta (Box 2, Item 24)
    - Kansas City #3, 1985-07-10; Beta (Box 2, Item 25)
    - Kansas City #4, 1985-07-10; Beta (Box 2, Item 26)
    - Union Democracy Tape #1, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 27)
      Burned-in time code, tapes 1-6
    - Union Democracy Tape #2, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 28)
      Burned-in time code, tapes 6-12
    - Union Democracy Tape #2, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 29)
      Tapes 6-12
    - Washington Raw Footage, 1986-03-25; Beta (Box 2, Item 30)
      Tapes 1-3
    - Washington Raw Footage, 1986-03-25; Beta (Box 2, Item 31)
      Tapes 5-6
    - JFK Footage, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 32)
      6/4
    - Southern Appalachian Labor and School Foundation, 1990-08-30; Beta (Box 2, Item 33)
    - P&H American Locker, 1996-03-15; Beta (Box 2, Item 34)
      Tape 1
    - Narration "R", Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 35)
    - UAW Tape 3 Narrations, Undated; Beta (Box 2, Item 36)
    - Troubled Partners Tape 1, 1998-07-14; Beta (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Troubled Partners Tape 2, 1998-07-14; Beta (Box 3, Item 2)
    - Troubled Partners Tape 3, 1998-07-14; Beta (Box 3, Item 3)
    - Merrimack Films Polaroid Archives Tape 1, 1998-06-24; Beta (Box 3, Item 4)
    - Merrimack Films Polaroid Archives Tape 2, 1998-06-24; Beta (Box 3, Item 5)
    - Merrimack Films Polaroid Archives Tape 3, 1998-06-24; Beta (Box 3, Item 6)
    - Merrimack Films Polaroid Archives Tape 4, 1998-06-24; Beta (Box 3, Item 7)
    - Merrimack Films B-Roll Stills, 1998-12-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 8)
      Tape 11
    - John Lisanti on Cam, 1998-12-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 9)
      Tape 12
    - Akron Ken Coss Tape 1, 1997-07-28; Beta (Box 3, Item 10)
      Tape 13
    - Akron Ken Coss Tape 2, 1997-07-28; Beta (Box 3, Item 11)
      Tape 14. With b-roll in garden.
    - Akron Firestone Plant, 1997-07-28; Beta (Box 3, Item 12)
      Tape 15. B-Roll.
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 13)
      Tape 22. B-Roll.
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 14)
      Tape 24. B-Roll, exteriors, camera displays.
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 15)
      Tape 25
    - Troubled, 1997-09-17; Beta (Box 3, Item 16)
      Tape 26. Auburn Cemetery.
    - Nashville Shoot Tommy Powell Tape 1, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 17)
      Tape 41
    - Nashville Shoot Tommy Powell Tape 3, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 18)
      Tape 43
    - Nashville Shoot Dan Bailey, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 19)
      Tape 44
    - Nashville Shoot Dan Bailey, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 20)
      Tape 45
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 21)
    - Taxes, Taxes, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 22)
    - Loose Bolts?, Undated; Beta (Box 3, Item 23)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; Beta (Box 6, Item 18)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; Beta (Box 6, Item 19)
    - Union Democracy, Undated; Beta (Box 6, Item 20)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 1, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 1)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 2, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 3, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 3)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 4, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 4)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 5, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 6, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 6)
    - Merrimack Labor Conference Tape 7, 1994-01-05; Beta (Box 7, Item 7)
    - Working Together Stills, 1994-04-04; Beta (Box 7, Item 8)
      1 of 2
    - Henry Bass Time Code Burn-Ins #1, 1988-08-25; Beta (Box 7, Item 11)
    - Henry Bass Time Code Burn-Ins #2, 1988-08-25; Beta (Box 7, Item 12)
    - Henry Bass Time Code Burn-Ins #3, 1988-08-25; Beta (Box 7, Item 13)
    - Henry Bass Time Code Burn-Ins #4, 1988-08-25; Beta (Box 7, Item 14)
    - Henry Bass Time Code Burn-Ins #5, 1988-08-25; Beta (Box 7, Item 15)
    - Trip: Canada Chrysler, Undated; Beta (Box 7, Item 16)
      Near beginning Canada
    - January Night-Line on Auto Industry Crisis, Undated; Beta (Box 7, Item 17)
      Brief on re-opening
    - Night-Line February 15, Undated; Beta (Box 7, Item 18)
    - Olympics, Undated; Beta (Box 7, Item 19)
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 7, Item 20)
    - Saturn, 1985; Beta (Box 9, Item 6)
      Labor Day, Chrysler.
    - Saturn, First Nine Minutes, Undated; Beta (Box 9, Item 7)
    - Saturn, Spring Hill, Undated; Beta (Box 9, Item 8)
    - Front Line GM Special, 1993-10-12; Beta (Box 9, Item 10)
      Channel 2.
    - Union Democracy, Undated; Beta (Box 12, Item 14)
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; Beta (Box 20, Item 13)
      Raw 2.
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; Beta (Box 20, Item 22)
      Raw 1.
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; Beta (Box 20, Item 25)
      Raw 3.
    - Partners, Audio Tape 2, Undated; Beta (Box 20, Item 27)
    - Steel Film, Contents of Audio, Undated; Beta (Box 21, Item 10)
      Tape #1.
    - Miscellaneous U.D., Undated; Beta (Box 22, Item 29)
      Japanese textile workers at very beginning.
    - Miscellaneous U.D., 1985; Beta (Box 22, Item 30)
      Teachers; Newspapers Strikes; Labor Day 1985.
    - Givebacks Update, Undated; Beta (Box 22, Item 31)
      Most of footage.
    - 1989 Eastern Air Strike, Beta (Box 22, Item 32)
      Early.
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 22, Item 33)
    - The Unemployed, Undated; Beta (Box 22, Item 35)
    - Givebacks TV Footage, Undated; Beta (Box 23, Item 1)
    - The Unemployed, Undated; Beta (Box 23, Item 2)
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 23, Item 5)
    - No Title, Undated; Beta (Box 23, Item 6)
    - Unions in Crisis, D.C. Shoot 1, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 1)
      Tape #1
    - Unions in Crisis, D.C. Shoot 1, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 2)
      Tape #2
    - Unions in Crisis, D.C. Shoot 1, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 3)
      Tape #3
    - Unions in Crisis, D.C. Shoot 1, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 4)
      Tape #4
    - Unions in Crisis, D.C. Shoot 1, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 5)
      Tape #5
    - Unions in Crisis, Narration and Stills, 1992-09-14; Betacam (Box 11, Item 6)
    - Unions in Crisis, Narration and Stills, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 7)
    - Unions in Crisis, Narration and Stills, Undated; Betacam (Box 11, Item 8)
    - Unions in Crisis, Narration and Stills, 1992-09-14; Betacam (Box 11, Item 9)
      Tape #4. First frame, work print.
    - Unions in Crisis, Boston Shoot, 1992-04-12; Betacam (Box 11, Item 10)
    - Unions in Crisis, Boston Shoot, 1992-04-12; Betacam (Box 11, Item 11)
    - Saturn Manufacturing Complex, Spring Hill, TN, 1993; Betacam (Box 18, Item 27)
      Media B Roll.
    - Saturn Packages, Undated; Betacam (Box 18, Item 28)
      Chan 5 tape.
    - Deere Harvester Works, Moline, IL, Undated; Betacam (Box 23, Item 3)
    - Partners: Bethlehem Steel and the United Steelworkers, 1996; Betacam SP (Box 5, Item 5)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; Betacam SP (Box 5, Item 6)
      Master. Stereo Mix.
    - San Diego IRRA Panel #1, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 21)
    - San Diego IRRA Panel #1, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 22)
      Tape 2
    - San Diego IRRA Panel #1, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 23)
      Tape 3
    - San Diego IRRA Panel #1 and Leo Gerard Interview, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 24)
      Tape 4
    - San Diego Leo Gerard and Dave McCall Interviews, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 25)
      Tape 5
    - San Diego Tom Wood Interview, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 26)
      Tape 6
    - San Diego Lynn Williams Interview, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 27)
      Tape 7
    - San Diego Lynn Williams and Paul Whitehead Interviews, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 28)
      Tape 8
    - San Diego Paul Whitehead Interview and IRRA Panel #2, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 29)
      Tape 9. Some B-Roll.
    - San Diego IRRA Panel #2, 2004-01-04; Betacam SP (Box 6, Item 30)
      Tape 10
    - Sparrows Point, Reel #1, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 9, Item 1)
    - Sparrows Point, Reel #2, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 9, Item 2)
    - Sparrows Point, Reel #3, 1995-11-30; Betacam SP (Box 9, Item 3)
    - Sparrows Point, Reel #8, 1995-12-01; Betacam SP (Box 9, Item 4)
    - Sparrows Point, Reel #10, 1995-12-01; Betacam SP (Box 9, Item 5)
    - Cleveland Shoot, 2005-07-21; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 23)
      Reel 1
    - Cleveland Shoot, 2005-07-21; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 24)
      Reel 2
    - Cleveland Shoot, 2005-07-21; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 25)
      Reel 3
    - Cleveland Shoot, 2005-07-21; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 26)
      Reel 4
    - Cleveland Shoot, 2005-07-21; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 27)
      Reel 5
    - Wilbur Ross NYC Interview, 2004-02-26; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 28)
    - Wilbur Ross NYC Interview, 2004-02-26; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 29)
    - Wilbur Ross NYC Interview, 2004-02-26; Betacam SP (Box 11, Item 30)
      Reel 3. B-Roll.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1983-07-15; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 1)
      Master. Mono.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1983-07-15; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 2)
      Duplication Master. Mono. No.16061.
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 3)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 4)
      Duplication Master. Mono. No.16062.
    - Partners Sparrows Point #2, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 5)
      Tape 11. Stereo.
    - Partners McKersie #1, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 6)
      Tape 022
    - Partners McKersie #2, 1996-02-16; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 7)
      Tape 023
    - Partners Lisanti #1, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 8)
      Tape 024
    - Partners Lisanti #2, Undated; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 9)
      Tape 025
    - Rustbelt Phoenix: Saving the American Steel Industry, 2006; Betacam SP (Box 12, Item 10)
      Stereo. PAL.
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1999; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 1)
      Master.
    - Troubled Partnerships, 1999; Betacam SP (Box 14, Item 2)